This XML file does not appear to have any style information associated with it. The document tree is shown below.
<config xmlns="http://www.onthemove-academy.org/schema/config" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.onthemove-academy.org/schema/config otma-config.xsd">
    <people>
        <person name="Erich Neuhold" title="dean">
            <introduction>
                Erich Neuhold is Professor at the Faculty of Computer Science at the University of Vienna and at the Faculty of Computer Science at the Darmstadt University of Technology. Until 2005 he was also Director of the Fraunhofer Institute for Integrated Publication and Information Systems (IPSI) in Darmstadt. Earlier he has been Professor at the University of Stuttgart and the Technical University of Vienna and he has also worked in research and management positions for IBM and Hewlett Packard both in Europe and the USA. His areas of expertise include distributed databases, object-oriented databases, databases for the internet (e.g. unstructured, semi-structured and structured), information retrieval, information visualization, workflow and business processes and their applications in digital libraries, cultural heritage, e-science, e-commerce, and e-government. He has published four books and about 200 papers. His work has appeared, among others, in the VLDB Journal, Information Systems, Acta Informatica and in many conferences as, for example, VLDB, ICDE, MMDB, ADL, DL, IRC, CAiSE, EC-Web, EURASIA etc. He has served in all capacities on many conference committees and was PC Chair and General Chair, among others, of VLDB, ICDE, OTM, WISE, SAINT, JCDL and ECDL. He was Chair of the IEEE TCDE and IEEE TCDL and was member and Chair of the ICDE Steering Committee and he is currently Chair of the JCDL Steering Committee. He is a Fellow of IEEE, USA and the Gesellschaft für Informatik, Germany and has received many other honors. He is currently Dean of the OTM Academy but has created and has been involved in a number of other PhD workshops in the past. He considers those efforts to be highly beneficial for the students presenting, but also the students in attendance. The benefits go beyond the usual Seminars offered inside of University curricula, as a number of senior person will be present for suggestions and comments, as opposed to a single ‘advisor’ in a University setting.
            </introduction>
        </person>
        <person name="Alfred Holl" title="faculty member">
            <introduction>
                Alfred Holl is professor at the Department of Computer Sciences at the Georg Simon Ohm University of Applied Sciences, Nuremberg, Germany. Homepage: http://www.informatik.fh-nuernberg.de/professors/holl/Personal/HollHome.htm His main subject is information systems. His areas of interest are all sorts of modeling, critique and theory of modeling, requirements engineering, epistemology (theory of knowledge), cognitive methods, languages and linguistics, history of mathematics, international university relations. He is faculty member of OTM Academy and a specialist for linguistic aspects.
            </introduction>
        </person>
        <person name="María Esther Vidal" title="faculty member">
            <introduction>
                Maria Esther Vidal is Professor at the Computer Science Department at the Universidad Simón Bolívar, Caracas in Venezuela Her current research interests include query rewriting, optimization and efficient query engines in emerging infrastructures particularly the Semantic Web, Semantic Grid and Linked Data; also resource discovery, service selection and composition techniques are among her main interests. Marıa-Esther Vidal is a Full Professor of the Computer Science department at the Universidad Simón Bolívar, Caracas, Venezuela. Professor Vidal received a PhD on Computer Science on 2000 from the University Simon Bolıvar. She has been Research Associate and Visiting Researcher at the Institute of Advanced Computer Studies of the University of Maryland, and Visiting Professor at Universidad Politecnica de Catalunya and University of Laguna Spain. Professor Vidal has participated in 8 international projects supported by NFS (USA), AECI (Spain) and CNRS (France). She has advised five PhD students and more than 45 master and undergraduate students. Professor Vidal has published more than 50 papers on International Conferences and Journals of the Database and The Semantic Web areas. She has publications on TPLP, AAAI, IJCAI, SIGMOD, EDBT, ISWC, ESWC, CoopIs, WebDB, ICDE, ODBASE, WIDM, DILS, DEXA, GLOBE, JBCB and SIGMOD RECORDS. She has been reviewer of: ICDE, VLDB, IEEE TKDE, DKE, CooPIS OTM, SIGMOD, ACM Survey, and has participated in the Program Committee of several International Conferences. She is faculty member of OTM Academy.
            </introduction>
        </person>
        <person name="Anja Metzner" title="faculty member and organisation chair">
            <introduction>
                Anja Metzner is a professor at the Faculty of Computer Sciences at the University of Applied Sciences Augsburg. Her current research interests include omnipresent web systems, mobile and pervasive systems, software engineering, system design and databases. As she received for herself some extraordinary supervision and phantastic help from the researcher community during her own PhD student time, she likes now to help others in this situation. As former German PhD student at the Middlesex University in London UK, she learned early about international teamwork and the advantages of networking together with other researchers all over the world. Consequently, she enthusiastically looks forward to the OTM Academy event, which she organises toghether with Peter Spyns.
            </introduction>
        </person>
        <person name="Peter Spyns" title="organisation chair">
            <introduction>
                Peter Spyns is researcher at the Vrije Universiteit Brussel and the Semantics Technology and Application Research Lab (STAR Lab), His main subject includes Knowledge engineering and modelling. His area of interests are Ontology learning evaluation methods, Human language technology and Ontology engineering methodology. If there are any questions you have regarding OTM Academy you may rely on him.
            </introduction>
        </person>
    </people>
    <events>
        <conference title="20th International Conference on COOPERATIVE INFORMATION SYSTEMS " abrv="CoopIS 2012" room="1">
            <description>
                Cooperative Information Systems (CIS) provide enterprises and user communities with flexible, scalable and intelligent services in large-scale networking environments. Building next generation CIS requires technical breakthroughs as well as dynamic, reliable and secure collaborative information technologies to overcome the tough challenges that traditional rigid distributed systems did not face. A particular challenge in modern enterprises and entire supply chains is providing flexible and real-world aware CIS that enable users to quickly react to environmental changes as well as to evolving needs (e.g., by continuously and dynamically adapting CIS). The CIS paradigm has traditionally encompassed distributed systems technologies such as middleware, business process management (BPM) and Web technologies. In recent years, several innovative technologies have emerged: SaaS, cloud computing, Internet of Service, Internet of Things, Service Oriented Computing, mash-ups, Web Services, Semantic Web and Knowledge Grid. These new technologies have increased the need for a tighter integration of data and knowledge with business processes, workflows as well as with collaborative process settings such as process choreographies. This trend is also reflected in areas such as data- or artifact-centric workflows and business process compliance as well as in finding new ways of analyzing data and processes in a combined manner. CIS applications are heavily distributed and highly coordinated, often exhibiting inter-organizational interaction patterns and requiring distributed access and sharing of computing and information resources. Typically they fall under the categories such as e-Business, e-Commerce, e-Government, e-Health, and e-Science. The CoopIS conference series has established itself as a major international forum for exchanging ideas and results on scientific research for practitioners in fields such as computer supported cooperative work (CSCW), middleware, Internet und Web data management, electronic commerce, business process management, agent technologies, and software architectures, to name a few. In addition, the 2012 edition of CoopIS aims at highlighting the increasing need for data- and knowledge-intensive processes. As in previous years, CoopIS'12 will be part of a joint event with other conferences, in the context of the OTM ("OnTheMove") federated conferences, covering different aspects of distributed information systems.
            </description>
        </conference>
        <conference title="2nd International Symposium on Secure Virtual Infrastructures" abrv="DOA-SVI'12" room="7">
            <description>
                DOA-SVI'12 is the second International Symposium on Secure Virtual Infrastructures, organized as a component conference of the OnTheMove Federated Conferences und Workshops. This year's OTM event will be held in Rome, Italy, from 10 - 14 September 2012. Current and future software needs remain focused towards the development and deployment of large and complex intelligent and networked information systems, required for the internet- and intranet-based systems in organizations, and covering a very wide range of application domains as well as technology and research issues. MOTIVATION: Distributed computation is undergoing a radical paradigm shift, where users and developers alike are becoming fully decoupled from the technology infrastructure where their applications are executed. Computations details are abstracted by an increasingly deep virtualization layer, veiling distributed execution by means of the same "cloud" that supports it. Together, the notion of Cloud Computing and the related one of service-orientation are enabling new business models based on the seamless provision of dynamically scalable, virtualized resources as services made available “over the cloud”, to be accessed via a web browser. For this vision to be realised, a number of problems need to be solved, involving the nuts-and-bolts of virtualization as well as the reliability, scalability, security and distribution transparency of cloud-based computations, and the abstractions leading their development (e.g. service composition versus on-line architectural transformations). Along with the rapid evolution of these fields, the Cloud vision requires a huge research and development effort in the underlying technologies, whose advances will broaden the scope of the Cloud's applicability. DOA-SVI 2012 will investigate all issues related to the potential of the Cloud notion as a metaphor for the future Internet Services, providing semantically rich service descriptions and seamless interfaces to (virtual images of) locally held devices and other technologies such as the traditional Web, distributed datacenters and peer-to-peer systems.
            </description>
        </conference>
        <conference title="The 11th International Conference on Ontologies, DataBases, and Applications of Semantics" abrv="ODBASE 2012" room="19">
            <description>
                The conference on Ontologies, DataBases, and Applications of Semantics for Large Scale Information Systems (ODBASE'12) provides a forum on the use of ontologies and data semantics in novel applications. Of particular relevance to ODBASE 2012 are papers that bridge traditional boundaries between disciplines such as databases, networking, mobile systems, artificial intelligence, information retrieval, and computational linguistics. We also encourage the submission of research and practical experience papers concerning scale issues in ontology management, information integration, and data mining, as well as papers that examine the information needs of various applications. This year, in addition to its traditional focus on the management of semantically-rich information, ODBASE will have special themes on large scale information management and analysis. We encourage submissions in areas that connect semantics with the entire data flow cycle: data acquisition e.g. from sensors and mobile devices, data stream processing, e.g., filtering and event contextualization, to dissemination, e.g., publish/subscribe.ODBASE'12 intends to draw a highly diverse body of researchers and practitioners by being part of the Federated conferences Event "On the Move to Meaningful Internet Systems 2012 (OnTheMove'12)" that co-locates three conferences: ODBASE'12, DOA-SVI'12 (International Symposium on Secure Virtual Infrastructures), and CoopIS'12 (International Conference on Cooperative Information Systems). ODBASE 2012 will consider two categories of papers: research and experience. Research papers must contain novel, unpublished results. Experience papers must describe existing, real-world scale systems; preference will be given to papers that describe software products or systems that are in wide experimental use.
            </description>
        </conference>
        <workshop title="7th International Workshop on Enterprise Integration, Interoperability and Networking" abrv="EI2N'2012" room="13">
            <description>
                Enterprises must collaborate in order to prosper in the current extreme dynamic and heterogeneous business environment. Enterprise integration, interoperability and networking are the major disciplines that study how can companies collaborate and communicate in the most effective way. These disciplines are well-established and supported by international conferences, initiatives, groups, task forces and european projects where different domains of knowledge have been involved from different points of views and according to a variety of objectives (e.g., technological or managerial). Enterprise Integration involves breaking down organizational barriers to improve synergy within the enterprise so that business goals are achieved in a more productive and efficient way. Enterprise modelling, architecture, and ontology are the pillars supporting the achievement of enterprise integration and interoperability. This seventh edition of the workshop is organized as a venue of experts, part of the OTM’2012 Federated Conferences (http://www.onthemove-conferences.org). It aims at identifying issues in applications of interoperability in enterprise integration and networking that will be developed in future research projects. A keynote speech and a plenary session will be jointly organized with CoopIS’2012 conference.
            </description>
        </workshop>
    </events>
    <hints>
        <hint title="Hall of Fame of our past PhD students">
            See more details under http://www.onthemove-academy.org/index.php/otma-phd-students-hall-of-fame
        </hint>
        <hint title="FAQ">
            See frequently asked questions under http://www.onthemove-academy.org/index.php/otmafaqs
        </hint>
        <hint title="Authors Kit">
            Find the authors kit under http://www.onthemove-conferences.org/index.php/authors-kit/camreadyws
        </hint>
        <hint title="Important Dates">
            You can find the actual dates under http://www.onthemove-conferences.org/index.php/important-dates
        </hint>
        <hint title="Tips for your paper">
            Please download http://www.onthemove-academy.org/images/documents/tips_paper.pdf
        </hint>
        <hint title="Tips for your poster">
            Please download http://www.onthemove-academy.org/images/documents/postertemplate.pdf
        </hint>
    </hints>
</config>